It's latex time again. I'm already wearing Ellen Harness, but I have a new outfit today.
A really special outfit with a coat made of latex and pennies and socks.
Stay ups. So high socks. Anyway before I am going to complicate it even more
let's dive into it and I'm going to get changed to show it to you.
This is the base outfit. We have these stockings, a panty which has kind of like neck holder part here in the middle and also on the sides.
So really interesting design and a triangle bra top. And all together it looks like a bodysuit I think.
good thing here is the panty can't slide down because it is kept in place by the straps here
in the neck and i think it's a cute outfit it's really nice but actually as i said it's only the
base i do have something to put on top so this is the coat it's transparent black or smoky black
And it has no arms, so it's more of a cape, I guess.
Doesn't work, by the way, so that's why I'm looking that way.
Okay, done. That is really quick and easy thanks to no arms and a buckle. And I think
it's a nice overall outfit now. So, let me check the mirror. Oh, it's really nice. I
I like the length.
It's actually a lot of latex sheeting.
I mean, there's a lot going on here.
Of course it sticks a bit to each other,
so maybe use a bit, I'll use a bit of a talcum next time
on the inside, I don't know.
Because I think if it's flowy, it's way cooler.
But yeah, it's a nice measure between the dress and the cape
and lots of details.
Also with the stockings, I don't think it would look that good without stockings.
Especially if they peek through, like when I do this.
So yeah, there's a lot going on.
I really like it.
And it's a nice new design, something to say.
I mean, there are always catsuits around, there are always skater skirts around, or tops,
or long sleeves, or whatever.
You see that on every party, all kind of photoshoots.
But this is something nice, this is new.
This is like, I love the design and the idea behind that.
And you could undress it, but you can also do everything you want to do with the cape
on.
The specialty here is the transparent latex. I do like transparent black or transparent purple or
colors in general. I'm not really a fan of natural transparent latex. And if you wash transparent
latex, a lot of people get scared then because they see whitish stains on their latex, their
transparent latex. And I don't know, maybe they think it's broke, whatever. It's actually a water
that the latex soaked in and you have to simply let it dry for a few more hours or days and then
these water stains will disappear so don't get scared by them all right do you like the outfit
check out alien harness if you do i will put the link in the description text they also have
harnesses and other outfits they do have catsuits they have a lot of items so click on the webshop
link click on subscribe and the thumbs up and check out my other videos thanks
to elian harness for sending this over and i will see you in the next video bye